My long, one-sided crush,
comes to its happy end.
To ask for anything more is thoughtless.
I'll be heading out now.
[3 Months Later]
Already?
Have a good day!
Hey, no waving my boxers around.
See you later.
See you.
See? Look at how lovey-dovey we are.
I need the whole world to hear it.
I'm washing his boxers,
but we haven't smooched, let alone have sex!
Seriously, what was up with that?
We're good with not getting physical, right?
Our relationship's not like that.
Faking our kiss at the altar?
What are we, actors in a movie?
No, even actors go further than that.
Getting physical with Ouji.
I'd never thought about it before.
But once a couple marries,
don't they normally...
What's wrong?
I thought you'd never...
do this sort of thing with me.
Dummy.
No, I...
I was saving it for our first night together.
Your voice. It's cute.
Haru?
Earth to Haru.
Did you hear a word we said?
- I am so sorry.
- Jeez...
Still getting lost in your thoughts, I see.
I'm so embarrassed...
How do you two know each other?
He's a graphic designer, and I'm a writer.
If I had to put a word to it, we're...
Old partners. They used to work together
back when they were rookies.
You'd daydream back then, too?
Enough about me.
What were you all talking about?
Just how sex is difficult to bring up
between married couples.
What inspired that conversation?
The article you three will be writing
about sexless women in their thirties.
Oh, right.
The Editor-in-chief
proposed we cover the topic.
Sexless relationships
are afflicting younger couples
for a variety of reasons.
- Interesting.
- It seems a married relationship
makes it more difficult to broach the topic.
It's probably because after marriage,
sex is seen merely as procreation.
I'm sure this all
seems farfetched for you
and your sexy musician husband, though.
If anything, I feel like the representative.
Huh?
T-The representative of newlywed couples!
I can't wait to hear what seasoned wives
have to say about their relationships.
[Episode 2]
They should really just interview me.
But sexless implies there was a "sex" before.
Then what does that make our relationship?
Sex...
Zero?
Even so, the Ouji I always dreamed of...
will be there as soon as I get home!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
This smell...
I made curry.
Want some?
I love him!
You really made this?
Why are you doubting me?
Your plating looks so professional.
I suppose that's your artistic sense
shining through.
It's the first time I made curry,
so I won't guarantee how it tastes.
Really? What suddenly inspired you to cook?
I saw the recipe on my friend's account.
Looked easy enough, so I went to the store.
You went to a supermarket?
Just give it a try.
I will.
Thanks for the meal.
So good!
Glad to hear it.
This is seriously delicious.
It has an ethnic taste to it.
Right? I thought curry was a difficult dish,
but this recipe was simple enough.
Hey! You spilled on your skirt!
What are you, a child?
Sorry.
What?
Living together has made me realize...
you're more put together than I thought.
You're honestly a bit maternal sometimes.
Say what?
Fine, no more cooking for me.
I was kidding! It was a joke!
And to think I even bought ice cream for us.
Really?
So sweet...
Is tonight another Something-Moon?
They got too many of those, I'd say.
People wanted to give them fun names.
Makes the moon less mystical, doesn't it?
Mystical enough to me.
Honestly, I'd call it a miracle.
Ouji.
I don't want this miracle to end.
No, never mind.
Whatever you say.
I can't ask why.
Being with you is so easy.
Huh?
I guess marriage isn't so bad after all.
Moving new muscles wore me out.
Thank you for cooking.
I'm headed to bed.
Good night.
Good night! Sweet dreams!
Haru?
Suzuki! Are you here for work?
Sure am. You here for an interview?
Yes.
Thank you again for attending our ceremony.
Of course. The pleasure's all mine.
- Thank you for marrying our Ouji.
- Huh?
When I first heard of the marriage,
I honestly thought he'd lost it.
But everyone's saying
he's really mellowed out nowadays.
Never thought a guy who played around
with girls like these, would marry.
"Keiko Kotani"...
Guess he was fated to find happiness
with a nice girl like you.
See you around.
R-Right.
I used to obsessively check
his exes' posts,
but I realize I don't anymore.
I'm so blessed right now.
[Everything about our Sex Lives]
We thank you for joining us
for an anonymous discussion today.
Please tell us all about your experiences,
to better our article.
We've been sexless for about 7 years now.
At first, I had made some efforts
to pick things back up again.
Likewise. But there was little point trying
when my husband wouldn't react.
What sort of "efforts" did you all make?
I tried watching an erotic movie with him.
I wore sexy lingerie for him.
I tried that, too.
He laughed in my face
when I tried to massage him, though.
That was my husband
when one of my toys went off.
We can only laugh with them.
Yes, I totally understand.
If you're comfortable enough
to laugh off the awkwardness,
finding happiness without sex
is entirely possible, isn't it?
- Thank you for your time.
- Thank you.
Haru, that wasn't the right thing to say.
Huh?
These women are earnestly worried
about their sexless relationships.
You can't make a "let them eat cake"
proposition to them.
It killed the vibe of the conversation.
I never meant it in that way.
I just think marriage
is something to be grateful for.
When marriage is the very thing
tying them down?
- What?
- They cannot ever have sex again,
unless they divorce their husbands.
Isn't that incredibly terrifying for a woman?
See you two back at the office.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't let her words get to you.
I'm sure a newlywed wouldn't get it.
The Chief often makes these "as a woman"
remarks when the topic is sex.
Or her favorite "you have yet to know
the joys of being a woman".
The joys of being a woman?
I'd honestly call her remarks a bit invasive.
Joys of being a woman?
- Take care.
- See you.
Get that makeup off quick.
Will do.
Bye for now.
You wouldn't happen to be free today, right?
[Haru]
It's rare of you to invite me out solo.
I'm sorry I took you away from your family.
I didn't expect you to be available.
Don't be, I'm happy to join you.
Besides, Chizuka's sleeping over
at a friend's place tonight.
Then your husband's home alone?
Tell him I'm sorry.
Why?
Your husband seems to really love you.
You two are like the ideal couple.
Not even. Our relationship's gotten dry
after being married 7 years now.
Dry...
Does that mean...
Never mind.
Can I order more cabbage?
- Sounds good.
- Excuse me...
You certainly aren't one
for emotional attachments.
Why stay? We're done with our business here.
Business, huh?
You don't ever feel compelled to stay?
Especially with how compatible we are.
Nope. I keep my emotional
and physical needs far apart.
Sex is just sex, nothing more.
Also, I gave it four tries,
but you yap way too much when climaxing.
Bye.
Akina.
[Masanori: Don't ignore me.]
You're so damn persistent.
You weren't responding to any of my texts.
We had sex once. Quit tailing me around.
Don't put it like that.
Our hearts were on the same page, right?
Do I need to repeat myself?
We were satiating our carnal desires.
Nothing emotional about that.
- Huh?
- "Hearts on the same page"?
I feel nothing for you.
No heart, no emotions. Nothing.
But we're dating, aren't we?
Excuse me? Of course not.
Bye forever.
You easy woman!
If you love sex so much,
why not buy a man for yourself?
That's not a bad idea.
What? An affair?
Keep it down!
Sorry.
I guess affairs really do happen in showbiz.
My team is working on a stage play,
with young actors all around.
They're all so youthful, and yet...
One of the actors is having an affair
with a married staff member my age.
What? How old is the guy?
23 years old.
So, quite a bit younger.
Doesn't the actor have plenty of young fans?
He does, but nothing that ever blooms
into a relationship.
Our staff are all tight-lipped,
and seeing them together
isn't all too strange.
It's nice that he won't ever
press for marriage, too.
Wow... that sounds so erotic.
I'm jealous.
Says the newlywed.
Actually, the reason why I asked to talk
is partly because of that.
Huh?
The thing is...
I currently lead not only a sexless life...
but a sex-zero one.
What?
Sorry, I'm not following.
You and Ouji haven't done it, even once?
Nope.
I figured something was weighing on you...
And I couldn't rope in Akina.
She'd only make a logical, sound point.
That, she would.
Fuyumi, what do you think is going on?
Are marriages like mine acceptable?
Well, marriages are different for everyone...
But what about marriage with no sex?
Zero sex. That's not a thing, right?
Maybe Ouji's a virgin?
He's not.
So you might think.
But maybe he was only a player because...
Nope. I've seen him doing it before.
- What?
- Back when he was still doing shows.
Ouji, are you here?
The after party will be at...
That is not the time to be charmed!
Aw, I can't help myself.
Gosh, why do musicians always do it out back?
I've seen him french-kissing
a different girl in public, too.
He was never picky about his partners.
Only Keiko Kotani
lasted over two years with him.
Two years at most?
And he was likely having flings then, too...
So why hasn't he done anything with me?
Why did he even marry me?
Ouji's thoughts are a complete enigma to me.
But what do you want from all this, Haru?
Huh?
You shouldn't be asking about what's normal,
or what Ouji's thinking.
The question is
if you want to have sex with him.
Sex...
I'm so sorry! I didn't mean to sound preachy!
I've had similar worries, so I understand.
You did?
Sex happens when a man lusts after you.
If they don't, then you lose purpose
as a woman, something like that?
That's exactly my worry.
Asking for it yourself is too pathetic.
What if he only shoots you down?
Exactly, exactly!
But first, you have to accept
your true feelings and desires.
Don't worry. Accept yourself,
and you'll feel a whole lot better.
Fuyumi, your beauty is telling.
What? Trying to hit on me?
You're like the shining image of a woman
who is honest with her desires.
And what are your honest feelings, Haru?
I...
I want to have sex with him.
I really do.
But are my desires so important
that I'm willing to ruin our relationship?
You're like the shining image of a woman
who is honest with her desires.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You kept me waiting, Fuyumi.
I can't believe you left me for a friend.
Sorry.
Jeez...
Hey!
I'm home.
What are your honest feelings, Haru?
I...
I was so smitten for this man,
I was blind to my own desires.
Every slight touch of his
made me crave for something more.
Yet I chose to put a lid on those emotions.
I...
I want to do it.
I want to have s...
"S"?
[Preview]